[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which English king was born in Pembroke Castle, Wales in 1457?", "correct_answer": "Henry VII", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry IV", "Henry I", "Henry VIII"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Audrey Tautou, famous for her role in Amelie, played Sophie Neveu in the film The Da Vinci Code. Which of the following actresses was originally considered for the role of Sophie?", "correct_answer": "Kate Beckinsale", "incorrect_answers": ["Christina Ricci", "Sarah Michelle Gellar", "Meg Ryan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fourth largest city in Canada (after Toronto, Montreal and Vancouver), as measured by metropolitan area according to 2006 estimates?", "correct_answer": "Ottawa", "incorrect_answers": ["Winnipeg", "Edmonton", "Calgary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Mel Brooks play more than one role in the movie Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these tiny bugs is considered the smallest beetle in the world?", "correct_answer": "Scydosella musawasensis", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Nanosella", "Vitusella fijiensis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the active volcano Sakurajima located?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Peru", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Ambrose Bierces satirical book The Devils Dictionary, what is called \u201cone of the sauces which serve the French in place of a state religion\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Mayonaise", "incorrect_answers": ["Ketchup", "Hollendaise", "Mustard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jellyfish are fish.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that in the movie Rat Race, casino owner Donald P. Sinclair placed a bet on who, among the high rollers, would throw up first on the airplane?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the movie Say Anything premiere?", "correct_answer": "1989", "incorrect_answers": ["1987", "1990", "1988"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most abundant element in Mercurys atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "Oxygen", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Helium", "Boron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following Steven Spielberg movies broke box office records at its release becoming the highest-grossing movie at the time?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Jurassic Park", "Jaws", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"]}]